https://www.coolhockey.com/us/privacy-policy

Language & Currency
Shop by TeamAnaheim DucksArizona CoyotesBoston BruinsBuffalo SabresCalgary FlamesCarolina HurricanesChicago BlackhawksColorado AvalancheColumbus Blue JacketsDallas StarsDetroit Red WingsEdmonton OilersFlorida PanthersLos Angeles KingsMinnesota WildMontreal CanadiensNashville PredatorsNew Jersey DevilsNew York IslandersNew York RangersOttawa SenatorsPhiladelphia FlyersPittsburgh PenguinsSan Jose SharksSeattle KrakenSt. Louis BluesTampa Bay LightningToronto Maple LeafsVancouver CanucksVegas Golden KnightsWashington CapitalsWinnipeg JetsAnaheim DucksArizona CoyotesBoston BruinsBuffalo SabresCalgary FlamesCarolina HurricanesChicago BlackhawksColorado AvalancheColumbus Blue JacketsDallas StarsDetroit Red WingsEdmonton OilersFlorida PanthersLos Angeles KingsMinnesota WildMontreal CanadiensNashville PredatorsNew Jersey DevilsNew York IslandersNew York RangersOttawa SenatorsPhiladelphia FlyersPittsburgh PenguinsSan Jose SharksSeattle KrakenSt. Louis BluesTampa Bay LightningToronto Maple LeafsVancouver CanucksVegas Golden KnightsWashington CapitalsWinnipeg JetsReverse RetroReady to ShipThird JerseysYouthMystery BoxREVIEWS
My Account
My Account
My Wish List
Create an Account
Sign In
USD
English
CAD
Login
Forgot Your Password?
Create New Account?
Or Sign In With
Sign in with Twitter
Create New Account
Password
Confirm Password
Create an Account
Back
Forgot Password
Please enter your email address below to receive a password reset link.
Email
Please type the letters and numbers below
Reload captcha
Submit
Go back
Privacy PolicyIntroductionCoolHockey.com is owned and operated by SilverCrystal Sports Inc. (“SC Sports Inc”, “We”,” Our”). The following describes CoolHockey's privacy policy (‘Privacy Policy”) regarding the information that CoolHockey collects when you visit the CoolHockey.com website (“Site”). This Privacy Policy also describes how and why CoolHockey collects personal Information (“Personal Information”) from you (“You, Your”) and will provide You with contract information should You have any questions or concerns about Our Personal Information protection practices. By visiting and using the Site, You are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy.Our Privacy Promise and Our CommitmentCoolHockey values Your trust in us and is committed to protecting the privacy of every person who visits and uses our Site. We promise not to sell, rent, barter, or share with any third party any personal Information collected during Your Site without Your prior written permission.The Personal Information CoolHockey GathersInformation That You Give Us: CoolHockey also receives and stores any information that you enter on the site or give Us in any other way. This information may include names, addresses and other personally-Identifying information of users of the site who purchase Products from us or send feedback on Our Product or ask us questions. WE use this information to better understand the needs of our clients and to serve our customers, as well as to send you additional information about promotional offers that may interest you. You can choose not to make such inquiries to CoolHockey or to purchase any Products if you do not wish Us to collect such information.Automatic Information: CoolHockey also receives and store certain types of information whenever You interact with the Site, For example, like many Web Sites, The Site uses “cookies” technology Cookies are small text files that record your computers unique Identification number and certain other information about you. No third party has access to this information about you or to do damage to Your files. If You would rather that CoolHockey didn’t use cookies when You visit the site, click here and we will help you turn them off.Protection of CoolHockey and Others: CoolHockey releases Personal Information when we are required to do so by law. We may also disclosure Personal Information based on Our good faith and belief that release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use; or protect the rights, property, or safety of CoolHockey, our users, or the general public.With Your Consent: By using the Site, You give CoolHockey permission to collect information about the pages severe to You as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If You make an inquiry to CoolHockey, You authorize CoolHockey to use the information that you provide to personalize the information that we deliver to You and to use Your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. Other than as set out above, You will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. We will not reveal Your name, address or other personally identifiable information to any potential seller, manufacturer, retailer or merchant associated with CoolHockey unless You explicitly consent.Also, from time to time, CoolHockey may contact You to request feedback on You experience using the site, to assist CoolHockey in improving the site, or to offer special promotions or savings to You as a Site user.Accessing Your InformationCoolHockey gives You access to the information that we have collected about You fro the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. To access Your personal information, please send us an e-mail at info@CoolHockey.comYour ChoicesYou can always visit the Site and browse without providing any Personal Information. However, You will be obliged to provide us with personal Information should you choose to purchase Products through the Services.CoolHockey welcomes Your questions and comments regarding this privacy Policy. Should You have questions concerns or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, or if You do not wish to receive e-mail or any other mail from us, please advise us by e-mail at info@CoolHockey.comRegarding ChildrenCoolHockey does not intentionally collect Personal Information such as names, addresses, telephone numbers or e-mail addresses from children. If You are under the age of 18, You must not give Your name, e-mail address or anything identifying information without consent of Your parent or guardian should contact us at (416)784-9190 ext 270. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our existing files.Terms and Conditions of Use, Notices, and RevisionsIf You choose to visit the Site, Your visit and dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on available damages and the application of the law of the Province of Ontario and the federal laws of Canada applicable thereto.If You have any concerns about this Privacy Policy and your privacy protection in the Site, please send us an e-mail describing Your concerns info@CoolHockey.com and we will try to resolve them.
CUSTOMER SERVICE
Shipping and Delivery
My Account
Returns
FAQs
Gift Cards
WHY COOLHOCKEY
Customization
Copyright © 2020 CoolHockey.com Powered by Silver Crystal Technologies. All Rights Reserved.
Top
